

# **MARVIN** ROSETE

Web Graphic Designer

### About Me

Web Graphic Designer with 5 years experience creating, maintaining functional, attractive and responsive website for business or marketing campaign using cms



0997 601 3084



Maben1120@gmail.com



Fourth Estate Subd., Barangay San Antonio, Sucat Parañaque City 1715

#### **SKILLS**

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT TOOLS







October CMS

Wordpress

WIX

# **DESIGN TOOLS**







Affer Effects

Illustrator

Photoshop



Canva

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **EnfraUSA Solutions Inc** WEB GRAPHIC DESIGNER 2018 - 2023

- Building and maintaining websites using October CMS.
- Doing Quality Assurance to all websites my team created
- Design online collaterals
- Managing the client requirements and communicating them effectively to our on-shore team.

# Thrive Web Media **UI/UX DESINGER**

2023 - Present (Part-time)

- Create Branding/Logo
- Create wireframes and interactive prototypes to visualize and communicate design ideas effectively.
- Design online collaterals
- Motion Graphics

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Premiere Computer Learning Center**

Information Communication Technology 2014 - 2016

#### Vocational

#### **United Christian Academy**

Computer Hardware Servicing NCII

#### **Premiere Computer Learning Center** Visual Graphic Design NCIII

#### **REFERENCES**

#### **JUNIUS REYES**

**Product Specialist** ConvertKit 09063915150

#### **Aaron Nikko Gonzales**

Web & Graphic Designer Sourcefit 09087832399